[{"question": "  so now, what is this now?", "answer": " guggly worm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  and this?", "answer": " glow-pop giggly jammer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  you make it so funny.", "answer": "  hey umm, what\u0092s this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  ohh, geller\u0092s got one hooked! ohh! looks like a big one! yeah, ohh! ohh!  it\u0092s the classic struggle between man and\u0097 someone knocked over a lamp.", "answer": "  that\u0092s all right. hey you guys, you know what\u0092s going to be great about the fishing trip this year? when my dad gets me out in the middle of the lake and gives me that, \"joey, what are you doing with your life?\" stuff. i can say, \"well, i\u0092m doing a movie with charlton heston dad. what are you doing with your life?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hey, joey, i don\u0092t think that you should leave chandler alone. i mean it\u0092s only been two days since he broke up with kathy. maybe you can go fishing next week?", "answer": " look, there\u0092s nothing i can do for him right now, he\u0092s still in his sweat pants, that\u0092s still phase one. y'know? i\u0092ll be back for phase two, i would never miss phase two.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " what\u0092s phase two?", "answer": " gettin\u0092 drunk and going to a strip club.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " how does going to a strip club help him better?", "answer": " because there are naked ladies there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " which helps him get to phase three, picturing yourself with other women.", "answer": " there are naked ladies there too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  would you give me one minute!! please. opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " so, these will match the jacket you picked out for me last week?", "answer": " um-hmm.  there we go. there it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  oh! you know what i need?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " gloves. brown, leather dress gloves.", "answer": " oh, okay. uhh, well let\u0092s see.  you\u0092re about\u0097well uh, this one is large. and this one\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " also large?", "answer": " yeah! okay, two larges coming right up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": "  rachel! could i have a moment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " i-i was wondering, my niece you see is in from london\u0097well shropshire really but y\u0092know\u0097well she\u0092s about your age i say. anyway i have tickets for the opera, die fledermaus, and i was wondering if you\u0092d like to keep her company this evening?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " sure. you got it. great!", "answer": " oh, good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " ohh! yes of course, thank you, thank you, thank you so very much.", "answer": " so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " gloves?", "answer": " ohh! right! right, sorry, i\u0092ll be right back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " uhh, actually y\u0092know what, i kinda\u0097i have to take off.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " but, i was curious; do you have any plans for tonight?", "answer": " no! nothing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i invested in this night-club and it\u0092s opening tonight, would you like to come?", "answer": " yeah! that would be great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " you\u0092re into hardcore s&m right?", "answer": "  well, i-i guess\u0097i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " kidding!  i\u0092m gonna get there early, but i\u0092m going to put you on the v.i.p list, okay? look for me.", "answer": " yeah, great, you betcha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": "  i almost forget the tickets, didn\u0092t i?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " for you and emily, tonight, die fledermaus.", "answer": " oh. oh, right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " i think you\u0092ll like it, it has two out of the three tenors.", "answer": " oh yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i can\u0092t believe kathy did this too me. i really, thought that she was the one. i tell you what, from now on i\u0092m never getting out of this chair, ever! okay? from now on, this chair is the one! you wanna what else is the one? my sweat pants!", "answer": " come on, man! just-just take the sweats off. okay? just take \u0091em off and we\u0092ll have some fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey-hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " catch any big fish?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh my god, you guys have no idea.", "answer": "  oh! god! wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " you stink!", "answer": " are you kidding?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah, three days on the lake without a shower. plus! i fell in that big tub of worms at the bait stand! hey, how-how\u0092s he doing?", "answer": " he hasn\u0092t gotten out of that chair in two days.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hey, see that? he just needed his pal to come home. all right, uh, i\u0092ve got to go memorise my lines.  me and charlton heston bright and early tomorrow morning! yeah-yeah!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey, monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " uh-oh, what\u0092s the matter?", "answer": " ohh, it\u0092s joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight. but, i already told mr. waltham that i would take his niece to this dumb old opera. so\u009a what are you gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know sweetie.", "answer": " no! help me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i can\u0092t! i have to work!", "answer": " phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " i would, but i get my morning sickness in the evening.", "answer": " ugh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " unless! she wants to spend the night holding my hair back for me.", "answer": " ohh, gosh. you guys, come on, this is\u0097i have to meet joshua! this is my one chance for him to see the fun rachel. y\u0092know the \"wouldn\u0092t it be great if she was my wife\" rachel. ohh, all right! are joey and chandler back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no, chandler\u0092s still in phase one, and joey\u0092s that thing you smell.", "answer": " ohh!  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " so\u009a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " ohhhh, come on!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i think she\u0092s here.", "answer": " no! wait! wait-wait! ross, please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " you want me to take some girl i\u0092ve never met to the opera so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy, hmm, that-that is a toughie.", "answer": "  ohh, she\u0092s looking down the hall. oh! she looked right at me! oh wait, you can\u0092t see people through that little hole, can you?  hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i\u0092ll be right there!  okay, ross, please come on! i thought we have moved on! i thought we\u0092ve gotten to a place where we could be happy for each other! i mean was that just me?", "answer": " all right, i\u0092ll do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh thank you! thank you, thank you, thank you!  emily?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " i\u0092m rachel green.", "answer": " thank goodness.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " there\u0092s been a teeny-teeny change in plans. it turns out that i\u0092m not free tonight. so\u009a", "answer": " really?! well, that\u0092s just lovely, isn\u0092t it? i must\u0092ve missed your call, even though i didn\u0092t leave the flat all day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh well, no i\u009a", "answer": " oh, no-no-no, that\u0092s not rude! it\u0092s perfectly in keeping with a trip that i\u0092ve already been run down by one of your wiener carts, and been strip-searched at john f. kennedy airport, apparently to you people, i look like someone who\u0092s got a balloon full of cocaine stuffed up their bum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " i-i-i think you look great.", "answer": " good night, it was very nice to meet you all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " i\u0092ll get her.", "answer": " please hurry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ohh!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " it kicked! i think the baby kicked!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh no wait, oh no, the elastic on my underwear busted.", "answer": "  oh my god! i overslept! i was supposed to be on the set a half an hour ago! i gotta get out of here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh wait, joey, you can\u0092t go like that! you stink!", "answer": " look, i know i feel asleep before i could shower and now i don\u0092t have time! they\u0092re just ten blocks away, if i run, i can make it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey\u0097whoa, slow down.  no, keep moving.  wow!", "answer": " so? how did it go with joshua last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " well, i didn\u0092t see joshua last night, but i did punch a girl in the face.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " the whole night was horrible, it was pouring down rain, and when i got there, there was no rachel green on the list, but there was a rachel greep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ohh! so, did you get to meet her?", "answer": " no, there is no rachel greep, but then this other girl overheard us and she was all, \"i\u0092m rachel greep! i\u0092m rachel greep!\" and he let her right in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " so you hit her in the face?", "answer": " no, she was already in, but then this big bitch behind me tried to steal my umbrella, so i clocked her. ohhh! i can\u0092t believe this, all i wanted was a few hours outside of work to see joshua, so he can go ahead and start falling in love with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  aww, pheebs.", "answer": " honey, that\u0092s you\u0092re name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hey! you\u0092re wearing pants!", "answer": " that\u0092s right! where are the guys? i\u0092m ready to get drunk and see some strippers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " it\u0092s 9:30 in the morning!", "answer": " they got a breakfast buffet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hello.  oh, hey ross!", "answer": " ooh, let me talk to him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh-oh, my god!", "answer": " well, can i just\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  shh!!  wait, what?", "answer": " she\u0092s shhing me! it\u0092s my phone and she\u0092s shhing me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " shhh!! please! what\u0092s he saying?", "answer": " he\u0092s with emily at a bed and breakfast in vermont!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " what? oh my god!", "answer": " what? who the hell is emily\u0097 noooo!! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " how\u0097how did end up in vermont with that awful witch?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " when we first met her, she was soaking, her feet were wet! who wouldn\u0092t be miserable? i\u0092m telling you when i got her into a dry pair of shoes, she was a totally different person.", "answer": "  ross! come quickly! there\u0092s a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " he had to go, there\u0092s a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard.", "answer": " i don\u0092t get this! she was horrible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " why do you care so much anyway?", "answer": " i don\u0092t care! all right, y\u0092know what i\u0092m just upset that i\u0092m getting nowhere with joshua that\u0097y\u0092know what still, you do not meet someone and go flitting off to vermont!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " well, when you first met barry, you flitted off to vail.", "answer": " oh, y\u0092know, would you just for once, not remember every\u009alittle\u009athing!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " so y\u0092know, uh, when\u0092s he getting back?", "answer": " a couple of days.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what are you doing?! chandler! you can\u0092t just go back a phase!", "answer": " yes you can. you\u0092re thinking about time, you can\u0092t go back in time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " well, look, why don\u0092t you just, why don\u0092t you do your phase two strip club thing with us.", "answer": " yeah, come on, we can be guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  no you can\u0092t.", "answer": " come on! let us be guys! maybe we want to be guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " y\u0092know you, you just stop being such a wuss and get those off and you come with us and watch naked girls dance around!!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  hey! joey tribbiani! i\u0092m here! i\u0092m here!", "answer": " calm down, we got time, we\u0092re running a little late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " look at that, charlton heston eating a liquorice whip!", "answer": " yeah, we loves \u0091em. i\u0092ve never seen him with\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  whoa! yeah, what the hell is that? what smells so bad?", "answer": " you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i can see why you think that, but ah, actually, you know who i think it is?", "answer": " you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " no-no, it\u0092s uh, it\u0092s heston.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " yeah, the man wreaks! smells like he went on a three day fishing trip and then ate some liquorice.", "answer": " there\u0092s no way he smells, he\u0092s the only one around here with a shower in his dressing room.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " really, a shower huh? and uh, which-which room might that be?", "answer": " the one with \"heston\" on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  okay, i\u0092ve got some ones, you wanna put them in her panties?", "answer": " no thanks, mom!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh, no umm, hi, that-that, you have to put that out, \u0091cause i\u0092m pregnant. the cigarette smoking guy:  well, maybe you and your baby should go to another strip club.", "answer": " ha-ha, it\u0092s not my baby, ha-ha-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " very good,  so good.", "answer": "  i really, really enjoyed it. very exotic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": "  well, i just checked our messages and joshua didn\u0092t call. i mean you\u0092d think he\u0092d be worried about me not showing up at his club. ugh, you know what makes it so much worse, ross is all happy in vermont!", "answer": " come on! look where you are!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "  when you get a sec, another round of daiquiris.", "answer": " remember, a virgin for me please.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh! and don\u0092t let me leave without getting the name of that carpet guy.", "answer": " ahh, come on! y\u0092know what\u0097y\u0092know what, i think i\u0092m just gonna go home and call kathy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " well, if you think it will help.", "answer": " no! that was a test! in a couple of hours i\u0092m gonna get really drunk and wanna call kathy and you guys are gonna have to stop me! and then after that, i\u0092m gonna get so drunk, i\u0092m gonna wanna call janice", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " you should! how is she?", "answer": " ohhh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " how ya doin\u0092?", "answer": " who in the hell are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i guess you wouldn\u0092t believe me if i said i was kurt douglas, huh?", "answer": " put some pants on kid so i can kick your butt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " no-no-no, no, no, wait. you see, i\u0092m an actor, joey tribbiani, i\u0092m doing a scene with you today, and well, i stink.", "answer": "  you\u0092re in this picture?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, i\u0092m one of the cops that won\u0092t work with you \u0091cause you a lose cannon. anyway, look, i\u0092m really sorry, but i stink!", "answer": " joey, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": "  every actor at one time or another\u0097opp!  every actor thinks he stinks, even lawrence oliver at sometimes thought he stank, bob redford won\u0092t even watch himself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh no-no-no, you don\u0092t understand\u009a", "answer": " listen to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh yeah, yeah.", "answer": " i don\u0092t know one actor worth his salt that didn\u0092t say at one time or another, \"god, i stink!\" hell, i just did a scene out there, first take, i stunk the place up. but, the important thing you must remember, no matter how badly you think you might stink, you must never, ever bust into my dressing room and use my shower! do you understand me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " wait a minute! take your pants.", "answer": " yeah. oh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " so, we did okay at the strip club, right?", "answer": " oh yeah, that was great. thanks to you, the hottest cocktail waitress there is quitting to teach the third grade!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  i can\u0092t believe it! he still hasn\u0092t called.", "answer": " who, josh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " it\u0092s joshua.", "answer": " what, he doesn\u0092t like josh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " no, i don\u0092t.", "answer": " all right, well i\u0092m gonna put my sweats back on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh no! wait! wait! okay, y\u0092know what, you were right, you were right. we really weren\u0092t great at being guys, but you know why? because we\u0092re girls.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " and do you know what girls are really good at?", "answer": " stripping!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " no, listening! sit! y\u0092know, maybe it would just really, really help if you would just talk.", "answer": " yeah, come on! what\u0092s going in on in there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " yeah. and y\u0092know, if you wanna cry, that\u0092s okay too.", "answer": " okay, look, i\u0092m gonna have to ask you all to leave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " come on! chandler!", "answer": " look, forget it. we tried, but phase three is a lost cause, okay? those strippers were insanely hot, and i couldn\u0092t picture myself with any of them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " yeah, i really liked that fighter pilot one.", "answer": " oh, candy! she was so spunky!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " y\u0092know, i think if i were going to be with a woman.  it\u0092d, it\u0092d be with someone like michelle, she was so oh, she was so petite.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " see, i don\u0092t know, for me it would have to chantal.", "answer": " oh, chantal!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh my goodness, she had the smoothest skin! i mean when i stuck that dollar bill in her g-string and grazed her thigh\u009a", "answer": "  phase three! i just achieved phase three!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " i am totally picturing you with all those women!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " that\u0092s-that\u0092s not phase three.", "answer": " well, i\u0092m there too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " well, are we all together? like in a group?", "answer": " stop it! you\u0092re killing me! i think i just moved on to phase four!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh! what is that? what is that?", "answer": " where i don\u0092t want to have a relationship ever! i just want to have sex with strippers and my friends!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " come on, let me see that smile.", "answer": " i don\u0092t wanna.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " please?", "answer": " i wanted to go to the strip club!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " i know, i know, but you\u0092re gonna have plenty of chances. there are literally thousands of women out there just waiting to screw me over.", "answer": " yeah, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " hey\u0097ooh so, how was vermont?", "answer": " emily is\u009aincredible. i mean there-there are no words to describe it, i mean the whole weekend was like a dream.  oh! and you! rach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh, hey!", "answer": " hey! you were so right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " uh, what you said, about us being in a place where we could finally be happy for each other.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " oh, hmm.", "answer": " i mean, i, i-i admit i-i wasn\u0092t quite there. y\u0092know, i mean the thought of you and that-that josh guy\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " joshua.", "answer": " joshua\u009aguy at that club, dancing and having a good time, the thought of it kinda\u009ay\u0092know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " yeah, i\u009a", "answer": " but now! i\u0092m there! i\u0092m totally there! i\u0092m-i\u0092m finally where you are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " oh, thank goodness!", "answer": " yeah, and-and thank you for emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " all right ladies, here\u0092s what we\u0092re gonna do.  you are gonna take off my clothes.  you two, go get the oils.  and you just constantly scream at the top of your voice, \"chandler\u0092s the king! chandler\u0092s the king!\"", "answer": " i-i wanna be with her,  i like her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s fine! go with your instincts, go with your instincts.", "answer": " wait, now, what am i doing again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " come on! would you please pay attention, i could wake up at any moment! the cigarette guy: hi, i\u0092m joshua, i\u0092m here to pick up rachel.", "answer": " no-no-no, that\u0092 not joshua.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}]